[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "My teacher really tries to make class activities as _____ as possible for all students.",
        "answer": "inclusive"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you tell me about the _____ of Taiwan’s solar power industry?",
        "answer": "development"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you think that the mining and oil _____ will stop causing pollution by 2030?",
        "answer": "industries"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who do you think the company will _____ to be the new manager?",
        "answer": "hire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you think studying all night before a test is the best _____ to get a high score?",
        "answer": "method"
    },
    {
        "question": "The _____ of new industries that don’t pollute the environment is one of the government’s top goals.",
        "answer": "development"
    },
    {
        "question": "On the first day of class, the teacher asked to write a _____ about our family.",
        "answer": "paragraph"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you have any idea how much pollution coal _____ causes each year?",
        "answer": "mining"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you know how much that company _____ its workers?",
        "answer": "pays"
    },
    {
        "question": "What study _____ did she say she used to get such a high score on the test?",
        "answer": "method"
    },
    {
        "question": "I can’t keep traveling to Penghu to see my girlfriend each week — it’s just not _____.",
        "answer": "sustainable"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does the _____ used in Taiwan’s power plants come from?",
        "answer": "coal"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times have you read that _____?",
        "answer": "paragraph"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did you know that before tourism, the biggest industry in Jioufen (九份) was gold _____?",
        "answer": "mining"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I learn more about cleaning up the water _____ in my town?",
        "answer": "pollution"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can I find a job that _____ well enough for me to buy a house in two years?",
        "answer": "pays"
    },
    {
        "question": "The United Nations has an _____ for improving the lives of workers in Africa.",
        "answer": "agenda"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you think your _____ might make finding a job more difficult?",
        "answer": "disability"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sam has been _____ for over a year now. Do you know if he is looking for a job?",
        "answer": "unemployed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you think that this new business can help poor workers earn more money and escape _____?",
        "answer": "poverty"
    },
    {
        "question": "Would you mind telling me how playing video games all night is _____?",
        "answer": "productive"
    },
    {
        "question": "How can I _____ this problem to my boss without sounding like I’m complaining?",
        "answer": "express"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you know what the _____ for today’s meeting is? I want to know what we’ll be discussing.",
        "answer": "agenda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Companies should make a place to work that will not _____ the workers, shouldn’t they?",
        "answer": "harm"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you think that rock over there is a piece of _____?",
        "answer": "coal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did you know that the number of the world’s people who live in _____ has been going down for the last 30 years?",
        "answer": "poverty"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you tell me why our electricity _____ are so high?",
        "answer": "expenses"
    },
    {
        "question": "Not hiring women for this job isn’t very _____, is it?",
        "answer": "inclusive"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you know if this company will hire a person with a _____?",
        "answer": "disability"
    },
    {
        "question": "Would you mind telling me how long you’ve been _____?",
        "answer": "unemployed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Our study group had a very _____ meeting yesterday — we got a lot of work done.",
        "answer": "productive"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you think we can make enough money to pay for our monthly _____?",
        "answer": "expenses"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of _____ do most of the people in this town work for?",
        "answer": "industries"
    },
    {
        "question": "When will the world’s leaders have _____ talks on cleaning the world’s oceans?",
        "answer": "high-level"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you think can be done to reduce air _____ in big cities?",
        "answer": "pollution"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you know how much _____ that factory is causing to the river?",
        "answer": "harm"
    },
    {
        "question": "When do you think the power plants in Taiwan will change from burning coal to a more _____ energy source?",
        "answer": "sustainable"
    }
]